sneakerhead.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy - Customer Service - Customer Service | Sneakerhead.com

## General

Sneakerhead.com is committed to protecting user privacy. When you register for an account, you may be asked to supply personally identifying information, including your name, e-mail address, mailing address, and phone number. The information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  1. To improve our website: We continuously analyze and update our site to improve the Sneakerhead.com user experience based on internally developed information and user feedback provided by you.
  2. To improve customer service: We use information developed through our website and its users to help us improve customer service request responses and support inquiries.
  3. To send periodic e-mail: We will only use the email address you provide for order processing and to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.
  4. To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

## Cookies

We employ cookies (small files transferred to your computer's hard drive through your browser, if allowed) that enable us to recognize your browser for capturing and remembering certain information. Cookies help us remember and process items in your shopping bag and compile data about traffic and interaction on the site so we may create an improved user experience in the future. Any information collected by Sneakerhead.com via cookies is not linked to any customer's personal information collected by us.

## Personal Information

Your personal information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

## Safeguarding Your Privacy

Sneakerhead.com maintains the safety of your personal information using several security measures when you place an online order, or otherwise enter, submit, or access your personal information. All credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and encrypted in the database of our payment provider. Following an online transaction, we will not your private information on Sneakerhead.com servers. This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Third Party Disclosures

We will not transfer, trade, sell or otherwise reveal personally identifiable information to others. Trusted third parties assisting in operating Sneakerhead.com, conducting business, or servicing user orders are exempt from this policy as long as they agree to follow our privacy policies and keep personal information confidential. We may release personally identifiable information when required to comply with the law, enforce Sneakerhead.com site policies, or protect our rights or those of others, or for safety reasons. Non-personally identifiable site visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, and other uses.

This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the [Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/details.html) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information.

Third-Party Web Beacons: We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!, [click here](https://reports.web.analytics.yahoo.com/optout,OptOut.vm?domain=a.analytics.yahoo.com).

## Consent

By using this site, you consent to our privacy policies and to the conditions specified in our [terms of use](http://www.sneakerhead.com/terms-of-use.html) section, which sets forth conditions for use of Sneakerhead.com, including warranty disclaimers and limitations of liability. In the event Sneakerhead.com changes any of these privacy policies, we will amend this page accordingly.

## Contact

If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy policy you may contact us at:

Sneakerhead.com  
12325 Imperial Highway #326  
Norwalk, CA 90650  
USA
